https://www.kelso-races.co.uk/contact/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
skip to main content
Home
Race Days
Saturday Afternoon Racing 202024th Oct 2020Wishing Well Chase Day 20207th Nov 2020Borders National Festive Family Day 20206th Dec 2020The Festive Fling 202029th Dec 2020
Events
Racing Guide
Going Report
Race Day Information
Owners & Trainers
Hospitality Packages
Plan Your Day
Beginners Guide
Keep Me Informed
Receive all the latest news, events and special offers direct to your inbox:
enter your email address here...
Home  >  Contact  >
Home
Race Days
Events
Racing Guide
Book Tickets
Contact
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Venue Accessibility
Privacy PolicyWe are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully & details of our privacy statement can be viewed by clicking the link below.
If you have any questions or comments about privacy, you should contact us via:
Tel: 01573 221221
Email: info@kelso-races.co.uk Downloads
Privacy Policy 2018
Racedays
View our raceday fixture list and plan your next visit.
Booking
Buy your raceday tickets online and pick them up before the race.
Hospitality
A quick bite or quality fine dining? Kelso has it all.
Events
The perfect venue for Weddings & Private Parties.
Receive all the latest news, events and special offers direct to your inbox :
click here to sign up >
Keyword Search
enter your search term here...
Like most sites this site uses cookies : By continuing to use our site you are agreeing to our cookie policy.close & accept [x]
